uh
this
hey guys and welcome back to another
video after the unboxing i thought it
might be a good idea
to add some product information to the
video to further clarify how this
microphone
would stack up to the competitors so i'm
going to start
by going to jlab's website and provide
some information on the product
so i'm going to start by going to chrome
and go to jlab
i should wear this one here
and i guess i can start by going through
some of these spotlight images
this is pretty uh clean simple design
pretty satisfying closing
on the tripod
um
yeah got the mute it's got an led ring
on the bottom
so when it's red there's a mute button
on the bottom and when the lady's red it
is
muted and then there's a coordinated
omnidirectional sound
the chord noid is blue and the omni is
green and you press and hold on the mute
button
to change that
um the blue coloration
inside the microphone is actually foam
so you would not need a
foam sleeve over the top of the mic
to give you a better sound quality
because it's already built into it
and then we can go down a little bit
here and
see we got a 24 bit depth and 96
kilohertz
sample rate with a two directional
pattern modes which is the
um omni and cardinoid
direction sound we've got two two
condensers here
with a quick mute button volume control
which
if i right now i'm recording on the
microphone
so if i turn the
volume control it's going to control my
windows sound
and if you had headphones plugged into
it into the microphone itself
um it would control the your headphone
volume level it's got a type c port on
it
and that would go to the to a type
usb type a plug to your computer
and pretty simple you just plug it in
it's good to go
um the one i have is this one right here
it's just the lowest level i just wanted
to see how it would stack
up against some of the other ones i was
debating on
getting and all in all
i'm pretty happy with it so far
this is the talk pro series
it's got a few other options it's got
different um
recording modes as well and then this
is the like the mid grade level
it's got more options than
the basic level but less options than
the high level
um the lowest one is about fifty dollars
the highest one is about 150 and the
mid is about 100 dollars
like i said this great sounding mic it's
got professional grade recording at 9600
kilohertz and 24-bit recording um
very clear detailed great dynamic sound
um i'm about a foot away from the mic
right now and
from what i can hear it sounds pretty
good for a
lower level microphone two directional
sound patterns
modes cardinoid and omni record knowing
to be for more like individual calls
gaming streaming voice over podcasting
that sort of thing
and omnidirectional sound is going to be
using all four microphones
inside the mic and that would be more
like for
group settings or for business calls and
stuff like that
um like i said there's a quick mute
button on the bottom
you just press and hold that to change
the directional sound
and press it once and the led will turn
red and then
it is muted there is also a 3.5 mil
aux input on the bottom with
real-time listening a zero latency
feedback for your headphones
plug and play 5 foot usbc connection
and it is on a 5 8 input swivel mounting
um tripod so you could also put that on
like a clamp on
desk swivel mount as well
with a 5.5 8 um
input thread on that standard size
it comes with this little swivel um
mounting hardware and the tripod itself
and the microphone and then the cable
and then you got the quick start guide
two condensers cardinoid omnidirectional
voice control
quick mute 5 foot usb c connection
transducer types got condenser pressure
gradient with usb
digital output it is a usb connection
20 hertz to 20 kilohertz
118 decibels max recording power
sample rates 96 kilos 24 bit depth
pretty small design i don't know about
the size of my hand
not very big pretty compact
it only weighs 130 grams total withstand
is 300
grams zero latency
on the headphone jack
and it also also comes with a standard
two year warranty
from the factory looks like they're
comparing it to the blue snowball which
is about seventy dollars you can pick
that pick that up right on
amazon or best buy or other computer
part stores will have them
but the top goes cheaper
and it's also got quite a few more
options than the snowball does
and whoever took this picture it looks
like the tripod is going to fall right
off the table there but looks like
it's um
coming to the end of the product
information here um
all this information here is in the
quick start guide
that comes with the microphone inside
the box
all the stuff i've gone over already you
don't have to install anything
it's plug and go you don't gotta worry
about installing any software or
anything
you're just going to make sure your
microphone is set to the top go
and if you're running any sort of
recording software like obs
is what i'm using you just got to make
sure that the default
microphone is set to the jlab
led controls type c input recording
setting
the 3.5 male aux output
is on the bottom and then you get your
volume control
and quick mute and if you press and hold
that button
it will switch the recording setting
blue is cardinoid green is omni and red
will
mean it is in mute
it looks like that's about it like i
said right now i am recording with
the microphone right now and
from what i can tell it's a pretty good
microphone
jlabs coming up in their products
and seems to be pretty good hopefully
hope i hope to be seeing a lot more jlab
products in the future and right now i
am not being sponsored by jlab
this is just a personal
product review so i
would like to thank you for watching and
please like and subscribe my video
and have a good day thanks for watching
peace